Good afternoon. Do you speak English?
下午好. 您说英语吗?
Wonderful.
太好了.
I'm calling from the United States.
我从美国打来.
I'd like to speak with Milos Hermann, please.
我想和Milos Hermann讲话, please.
Yes. Thank you.
Yes. 谢谢.
Hello Milos!
你好, Milos!
This is Anne Holland, from the Sheraton Boston.
我是Anne Holland, 来自波士顿的Sheraton.
Yes, me too. How are you?
是的, 我也是. 你好吗?
I'm very well, thank you.
我很好, 谢谢.
Excuse me?
No, I'm calling from Boston.
不是, 我是从波士顿打来的.
We'll have our arrival dates very soon.
我们很快就会知道到达的日期了.
Milos, I wonder if there's an interesting theatre or club we can go to while we're in Prague.
Milos, 我想知道在布拉格(Prague)有没有好的剧院或俱乐部,我们到那儿时可以去.
We can? Excellent.
我们可以? 太好了!
Good idea. We can lunch at the hotel restaurant by all means,
好主意. 我们完全可以在饭店的餐厅吃午饭,
but then let's get into town for drinks and dinner.
然后去市中心喝酒和吃晚饭.
Milos, tell me, is there a hair salon at the hotel?
Milos, 告诉我,饭店里有美发厅吗?
I see Hm.
我明白了. Hm.
My hair doesn't travel very well.
旅行时我的发型总是保持不好.
Yeah, hat shop is a solution...
Yeah, 帽子是个解决的办法...
No, I don't think a wig is necessary.
No, 我不认为有必要戴假发.
OK then.
Yes. I look forward to it. Good bye.
Yes. 我很期待去那儿.  再见.
Maybe I do need a wig.
也许我的确需要一顶假发